{
    "id": "376a45eccae74a158f5a20ab514393a8",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… she was ill, she could not go to school.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81805ff2d05f45d9b1c54db24a133a76"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a rich woman ........................ she does not help anyone.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "who",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "219c652fa5d84863acc166f542d46dcf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stand up .......................... speak for yourself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "if",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a2a6bd58e00f4423968a0b05625fa9f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… she said made no sense to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79f91d8fb20649d0a314a7e2d82d5f39"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an atheist ……………………. does not believe in the existence of God.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac21f106d9a74f159ef66321d3688860"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... she arrives I will give her your message.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9b3f0408db2d44f5933cec789354fd33"
        },
        {
            "question": "The experience was .......................... painful ............................... recovery seemed difficult.",
            "description": "So...that... expresses cause and effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "so... that",
                "such...that",
                "too...to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "628a4f3af3084697aff24a059065e3fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ........................... cat was missing went from house to house looking for it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "f2d397d53a8c4e37887891525c367121"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was …………………… a wonderful experience that I still remember it vividly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9e5bdeb8f414fba9b3e064483284bea"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. did she arrive than I handed her the parcel.",
            "description": "No sooner is used in a comparative structure with than.",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb8024c535fe48cb81f762d7f2e18491"
        },
        {
            "question": "She acts ............................. she was rich.",
            "description": "As if and as though are used to say how a situation looks like. ",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9d9c6f780224e5091f952b91b2b9f87"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me ............................ there was anything she could do for me.",
            "description": "Either if or whether can be used to introduce an yes/no question. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1452232d44e48389104a6a30687f5ff"
        }
    ]
}